Finding Aid for Center for Japanese Studies (University of Michigan) Records 1945-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio-Visual Materials 1945-1991, 3 linear feet
  - Photographs
    - Kibitsu Shrine Visit 1954 (Box 15)
    - Maps, (Negatives) undated (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box 15)
    - Okayama Field Station
      - Bonisteel and Niehuss Visit; Jiro Taguchi Wedding 1954-1955 (Box 15)
      - Facilities Undated (Box 15)
      - Staff 1950-1954 (Box 15)
      - Parties and Social Affairs circa 1950-1952 (Box 15)
    - Emperor Akhito's Visit 1953 (Box 15)
    - Ambassador Togo's Visit 1977 (Box 15)
    - International Automotive Industry Visitors 1988 (Box 15)
    - Motohiro Kondo's visit 1988 (Box 15)
    - Shumpo Akashi, calligrapher 1988 (Box 15)
    - Graduation of CJS students 1991 (Box 15)
    - Japanese Music Study Group undated (Box 15)
    - Village Japan
      - Illustrations, 6 folders (Box 15)
      - Captions and Proofs (Box 15)
    - Center For Japanese Studies Photo Album 1978-1995 (Box 19)
  - Negatives
    - Village Japan Negatives, 2 folders (Box 16)
      (4x5 and 1 roll of 35mm black and white film and 35mm strip negatives)
  - Slides, 4 folders; 25 sheets
    - Slides of Village Japan
      - General
        - Scenery, pretty; Obara Ike May 1950, A (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Scenery, Inland Sea, Tsu Kubo-gun, Shoson, Iwakwa Jinja dolmen April 1950, B (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Topography-Land Use, C
          - Hatake-Niiike June 27, 1951, Cl (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
          - Niiike-Path up hill, palms November 1950, C2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
          - Niiike-Hill dug back for more space August 1, 1951, C3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
          - Un-labeled; man in grain field, C4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Transportation-Niiike, view of plain by Takeshi's house November 1950, D (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - City streets and shops (not received), E (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Industry and Labor, Kibitsu-hiko shrine January 1954, F (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Re. center, Okayame (not received), G (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Animal care, Tsutsu farmer with plow and Korean ox. Old woman with sun hat August 1950, H (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Fertilizer, cultivation (not received), J (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
        - Rice, K
          - Niiike-removing rice seedlings from seedbeds for transplanting June 23, 1950, Kl (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
          - Niiike paddy November 11, 1951, K2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 1)
          - Niiike Beginning of rice Harvest 1950, K3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Okayema; Niiike-I-gusa and new rice, early June 1950, K4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-cutting rice November 1950, K5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-paddy, October. 8 1951, K6 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-paddy November 6, 1951, K7 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-paddy, rice transplanting, end of June 1950, K8 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
        - Wheat-ripening mug, above Kato Tadamatsu's house, Matsunagi June 1951, L (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
        - Rush, M
          - Niiike-placing I-gusa on road July 20, 1951, Ml (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-bunching and laying I-gusa on road July 1951, M2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-bunching I-gusa July 20, 1951, M3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-placing I-gusa on road, July 20, 195, M4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-bunching I-gusa July 24, 1951, M5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike cutting I-gusa July 24, 1951, M6 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Near Niiike-I-gusa on bicycle August 31, 1951, M7 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-placing I-gusa on road July 20, 1951, M8 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike turning and drying I-gusa July 24, 1951, M9 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-starting to bunch and tie I-gusa July 24, 1951, M10 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-cutting to bunch and tie I-gusa, July 24, 195, M11 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
        - Miscellaneous Crops, N
          - Niiike-Hatake October 8, 1951, N1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-drying gourd in Sensei's yard August 1951, N2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-Sensei in his dry field June 23, 1951, N3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-Hatake September 20, 1951, N4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-Hatake November 6, 1951, N5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-Chicken-grass, sesame, children August 23, 1950, N6 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-Threshing naked barley May 29, 1950, N7 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Kawaoka-Natane mugi beyond May 25, 1951, N8 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - -Niiike-Isamu's vegetable garden May 10, 1951, N9 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Sensei by neighbor's hemp June 23, 1951, N10 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
        - Processing, P
          - Kamo-son, houses, strawshacks June 12, 1950, P1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 2)
          - Niiike-scarecrow September 28, 1951, P2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-Mugi beyond, Akashi Sendo, drying clay. May 11, 1951, P3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Fishing, Q
          - Hiroshima-oyster beds November 1950, Q1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Takashima-(Okayama) Fisherman collecting seaweed from boat July 1950, Q2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Irrigation, R
          - Taisho pond August 23, 1951, R1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-irrigation pond July 20, 1951, R2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Costumes, T
          - Unidentified, Tl (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Arifuku Joshin in priest's funeral regalia June 1951, T2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Children in road, Niiike August 1950, T3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Pilgrim at Koboji May 1950, T4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Woman in Lagitojin (winterwear) Mr. Koya winnowing August 1950, T5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Gardens, U
          - Niiike-new Neya, Nov, U1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-Sensei's shed, Persimmon Tree, U2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Architecture-fine buildings, Mori Castle ruins on Hisashiyama August 23, 1950, V (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Architecture-Domestic, W
          - Sensei's House-Niiike May 1950, W1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-Takeshi's new house July 1950, W2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-New Neya November 6, 1951, W3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike New house and black fence set in paddy scene July 1950, W4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - House construction, WA
          - Niiike-, Mayor H. Asae's new cow shed, an amateur construction, before thatching, walling March 1950, WA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-Rethatching I-Kokuji's house April 1950, WA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-yard of Tadashi's house July 1950, WA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Okayama-tile making, en route to Niiike April 1950, WA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-Hiroshi's new barn, foundation and lumber January 1951, WA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-New thatch roof, Shimobayashi September 1950, WA6 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Unidentified (thatcher?), WA7 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-new house July 20, 1951, WA8 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-barn and drying area June 1950, WA9 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Unidentified house under construction, WA10 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niijke--H. Tadashi's house July 1950, WA11 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
          - Niiike-Hajime's front gate August 1950, WA12 (Box 16, Othertype No. 3)
        - Roadside shrine at K. November, 1950, X1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Roadside shrine at K. November, 1950, X2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Buddhist priest (Aritaku Joshi) Matsunagi April 1951, Y1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Kokubunji, Y2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Okayama-Kokubunji not far from Niiike April 1950, Y3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Ancestors (not received), Z
          - Niiike-group of children my, Mayor's house April 1950, ZE1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
          - Okayama-looking NE from Sake Factory August 2, 1951, ZE2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
          - Kochi-ken-Makiyama river mura Odochi October 25, 1951, ZE3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Festivals (not received), AF (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Fall Festival Public Participants (not received), AFP (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - recreation (not received), RE (Box 16, Othertype No. 4)
        - Ainu-Community /Piratori-son, Hokkaido March 1951, AA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Ainu-salt field February 1951, AA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Ainu-meat storage/cages at Museum of Ethnological Society of Hoya August 1951, AA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Mt. Fuji-from Hakone barrier at L. Hakone on Old Tokaido March 1950, AA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Mt. Fuji-from S. Side of Hakone Pass March 1950, AA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Mt. Fuji-view across water, AB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Inland Sea-cruise May 1950, AB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Inland Sea-coast August 1950, AB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Inland Sea-valley off Inland Sea, E. Hiroshima Ken, [?] September 1950, AB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Inland Sea-tai fishing May 1950, AC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Inland Sea-view of hillside May 1950, AC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Higashi-mura-house of Fugimoto along path to Matsunagi August 1951, AC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Matsunagi-early morning roof scene November 1950, AD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Matsunagi-woman carrying tobacco, AD2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Matsunagi-roof and racks of drying rice, AD3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Matsunagi-slope cultivation, AD4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
        - Matsunagi-elevated house sites against mountainside, AD5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 5)
      - Kochi-Ken October 25-26, 1951 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-map legend October 25, 1951, BA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-map, BA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-map low grade production after 5 regions. October 26,1951, BA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-city. Soil map legend, October 26,1951, BA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-city soil map, October 26,1951, BA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-plain-Eastern part legend, October 26,1951, BB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-plain-Eastern part legend, map of, October 26,1951, BIJ 2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Map legend. Low grade production after five regions, October 26,1951, BB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-plain "Bad environment for agriculture, October 26,1951, BB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken. Cape Murato [?] October 26, 1951, BB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken. Cape Murato [?] October 26, 1951, BC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken. Cape Murato [?] October 26, 1951, BC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken. Cape Murato-Hano Town, Rocks showing level of sea 200 years ago, October 26,1951, BC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken-Murator Saki town/Takaoko, tarred ropes, BC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken-Murato Saki town-Takaoko, Sea Wall, BC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken-Makiyamamura-trees cut this summer, map, BD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken-Makiyamamura-trees cut this summer, map, BD2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken-Makiyamamura-trees cut this summer (sugi-10 years old), BD3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Ken-Monabe River Valley-W Daicho-mura/Kumigun/Nagano Aza October 25, 1951, BD4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 6)
        - Kochi-Kera Aza, Keru St. SW, 2 rice crops, October 25 1951, CA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kochi-Kera Aza, Keru St. NE, 1 rice crops (Straw in bkgd.), October 25 1951, CA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kochi-Tei Harbor, October 26, CA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kochi-Near Tei Harbor, burnt & green bamboo, October 26, CA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kochi-Birafu Machi/Shimoneji Aza Narus Slopes, October 25, CA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kochi-Karyoso. Nahari machi basket for carrying live Ponito bait, October 26, CB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kochi-Yamada machi from Kagami bridge, October 25, CB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
      - Kokubunji
        - Kokubunji, September 24, CC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kokubunj-Misu Village, Nov 25, CC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kokubunji-dances, September 24, CD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kokubunji-dances, September 24, CD2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kokubunji-dances, September 24, CD3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kokubunji-dances, September 24, CD4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
        - Kokubunji-dances, September 24, CD5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 7)
      - Niiike
        (includes som Oukaido and Okayama)
        - Niiike-east from hill November 22, 1951, DA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike east from hill November 6, 1951, DA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Oukaido-Kasu kabe town December 8, 1951, DA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-Datake November 22, 1951, DA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-Datake November 22, 1951, DA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-paddy, November 6, DB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-paddy, November 11, DB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-Spring plowing for rice seed bed-with con May 1950, DB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-beginning to gather I-guga [?] bunching and tying July 24, 1951, DB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-Eyre, Dr. Hall, & informant April 1950, DB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-drying magi [?] June 11, 1951, DC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike--New Neya [?] November 22, 1951, DC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-drying rice at Niiike November 1950, DC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-Hiroshi's new barn-mid-point in construction January 1951, DC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike pre-harvest shot-Daikon, bamboo November 1950, DC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-rice harvest-general shot November 1950, DD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-fire tower- April 1950, DD2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-house roof detail February 1951, DD3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-cemetery and Einoike January 1951, DD4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-beginning of harvest-General Hain November 1950, DD5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 8)
        - Niiike-spring harvest scene January 12, 1950, EA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-Hatake July 20, 1951, EA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-rear (North) side of Kenshiros unfinished house April 1950, EA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-I. Ishita cleaning ditch-sugar cane, taro, kampyo August 23, 1950, EA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Okayama-cemetery along road to Niiike April 1950, EA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-Abac-san with flowers in front of his house April 1950, EB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-from Oyama August 23, 1951, EB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy fields June 23, 1951, EB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy June 11, 1951, EB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy-mugi April 16, 1951, EB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-dry field April 16, 1951, EC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy-mugi May 11, 1951, EC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-dry fields May 11, 1951, EC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy-mugi May 21, 1951, EC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-dry field May 21, 1951, EC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy-mugi May 31, 1951, ED1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy-mugi June 11, 1951, ED2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-dry fields May 31, 1951, ED3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy June 11, 1951, ED4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-hatake June 23, 1951, ED5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 9)
        - Niiike-paddy June 23, 1951, FA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-paddy July 24, 1951, FA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-paddy July 20, 1951, FA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake July 20, 1951, FA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake July 24, 1951, FA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-paddy August 1, 1951, FB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 1 1951, FB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 13 1951, FB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-paddy, August 13 1951, FB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-hatake, August 21 1951, FD1-5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 10)
        - Niiike-Hatake September 28, 1951, GA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-New Neya September 28, 1951, GA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-paddy October 18, 1951, GA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-New Neya October 18, 1951, GA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-Hatake October 18, 1951, GA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-east from hill October 18, 1951, GB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-hatake November 6, 1951, GB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-paddy November 22, 1951, GB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-mugi May 11, 1951, GB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-dry field May 21, 1951, GB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-dry fields May 21, 1951, GC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-paddy-mugi May 21, 1951, GC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-Hatake-dry fields May 31, 1951, GC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-dry field- May 21, 1951, GC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-dry fields June 11, 1951, GC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-dry fields June 11, 1951, GD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-Hatake-dry fields June 23, 1951, GD2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-dry field June 11, 1951, GD3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-paddy June 20, 1951, GD4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-Hatake June 24, 1951, GD5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 11)
        - Niiike-Hatake August 21, 1951, HB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy August 23, 1951, HA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy August 23, 1951, HA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy August 17, 1951, HA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy August 21, 1951, HA52 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy August 23, 1951, HB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy, September August 14, 1951, HB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-Hatake September 14, 1951, HB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-drying day, New Neya-seed bed, mug, beyond May 11, 1951, HB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-Rice seedlings-New Neya May 21, 1951, HB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-rice seedlings in front of New Neya June 11, 1951, HC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy-New Neya June 23, 1951, HC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy-New Neya July 7-20, 1951, HC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-paddy by New Neya August 24, 1951, HC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-New Neya August 1, 1951, HC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-New Neya August 13, 1951, HD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-New Neya August 23, 1951, HD2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-New Neya, August 13 1951, HD3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-from hill August 31, 1951, HD4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-from hill September 24, 1951, HD5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 12)
        - Niiike-gathering dried I-gusa July 24, 1951, IA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-shaking short stems out of cut I-gusa 1951, IA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-turning I-gusa over July 24, 1951, IA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-I-gusa drying on road to Niiike July 24, 1951, IA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - turning I-gusa over July 24, 1951, IA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-close up of I-gusa May 11, 1951, IB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-shaking I-gusa for short stems and tying I-gusa July 24, 1951, IB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-shaking and tying I-gusa July 24, 1951, IB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-tied bundles of dried I-gusa July 24, 1951, IB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-turning I-gusa over 1951, IB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-clay-water for dipping I-gusa July 20, 1951, IC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-Masao Hiramatsu wearing Tatami August 21, 1951, IC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-Hatake August 1, 1951, IC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-dry fields May 11, 1951, IC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
        - Niiike-paddy September 14, 1951, IC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 13)
      - Nikkokaido
        - Nikkokaido December 11, 1951, JA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido December 11, 1951, JA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido December 11, 1951, JA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido-Iuraichi size of log-Noh for scale December 11, 1951, JA4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido-Iuraichi size of log-Noh for scale December 11, 1951, JA5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido-Iuraichi size of log-Noh for scale December 11, 1951, JB1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido-, Marugame (Shikoku)-tori pattern, November 24, JB2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Nikkokaido-, Marugame (Shikoku)-tori pattern-south November 24, 1951, JB3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
      - Oukaido
        - Oukaido-20 miles north of Tokyo December 8, 1951, JB4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-20 miles north of Tokyo December 8, 1951, JB5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-near Kamitakamo village December 8, 1951, JC1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-near Kamitakamo village December 8, 1951, JC2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-near Kamitakamo village December 8, 1951, JC3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-Kasukabe town December 8, 1951, JC4 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-Kasukabe town December 8, 1951, JC5 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
        - Oukaido-Noga Village December 1, 1951, JD1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 14)
      - Orayama
        - Orayama-skyline in twilight November 1950, KA1 (Box 16, Othertype No. 15)
        - Orayama-looking NW from fire tower, August 2, KA2 (Box 16, Othertype No. 15)
        - Orayama-near Kurashiki city-Mani Shopping St. August 1950, KA3 (Box 16, Othertype No. 15)